Welcome to KapiMart — your new favorite online store.
In this quick tour, we'll show you how to find products,
place orders, and track your deliveries.
Start by browsing our categories. We've organized everything
from electronics to kitchen essentials.
Found something you like? Click "Add to Cart" to save it.
You can keep shopping or check out right away.
At checkout, enter your shipping address and payment details.
We accept all major credit cards and digital wallets.
Once your order is placed, you'll receive a confirmation email
with a tracking number.
Track your package in real time from the "Order History" page.
You'll get notifications at every step.
Need to return something? No problem.
Go to your order, click "Return Item," and follow the steps.
Our support team is available around the clock.
Reach us via chat, email, or phone — whatever works for you.
That's it! You're all set to start shopping.
Enjoy free shipping on your first order with code WELCOME.